<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on Ibrafdj</title>
    <link>https://www.ibrafdj.com/en/tags/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on Ibrafdj</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.ibrafdj.com/en/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.ibrafdj.com/en/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.ibrafdj.com/en/page/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure &gt;&lt;img style=&#34;display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&#34; src=&#34;https://www.ibrafdj.com/ibra.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;figcaption style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;Hello there!&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I started blogging back when I was in high school in 2015 by writing short fictional stories for &lt;a href=&#34;http://simpleminded-thinker.blogspot.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;my very first blog&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA; (I was young and dumb; please be nice). But this hobby died out pretty soon as I graduated high school and entered college.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Flash forward to 2020, when a pandemic struck the world, and for a while, everyone just stayed in peace and quiet at home. There was no better time to revive a dead hobby. So, I started writing again and launched &lt;a href=&#34;https://ibrafdj.wordpress.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;my second blog&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;. This time I focused on writing non-fiction because college life just sucked all the creativity out of me, I guess. I graduated from college a couple of months later; and you guessed it, my blogging hobby died with it (again).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Review of Crash Landing on You (2019)</title>
      <link>https://www.ibrafdj.com/en/blog/a-review-of-crash-landing-on-you-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.ibrafdj.com/en/blog/a-review-of-crash-landing-on-you-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have never watched a single Korean drama series before Crash Landing on You.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That sums up pretty much all the qualifications that I have in writing this review. I have no prior knowledge of any K-drama tropes, character archetypes, culture, etc. This gives me an outside look and a fresh new perspective of this widely-acclaimed series. A perspective that I am willing to share in this spoiler-free review of Crash Landing on You!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
